Anochan karuta
Okay, next please.
He started wearing a hat.
He's wearing a hat... all of a sudden.
It's not a good connection.
Normally, the hat is put on in front of the other one.
You're an inspiring girl.
Nononononononononononononononononononononononononononononononononononon
Now that you can say it
And then and then and then
Come on, girl who stays
That channel this time
Short version.
Okay, I'll pull it.
Wood
Wood.
Stone.
Let's make it lame.
Wood.
There's a lot of different kinds of wood.
It's hard to draw, but it's a little hard to start with.
I've got it!
Let's see the tree cult.
Wood! Let me see the tree cult!
A tree.
What is it?
It's in the safe.
What do you mean?
The most important thing.
The treasure.
He's keeping someone else's.
Yeah, your own.
Voluntarily.
Voluntary storage.
This is great, isn't it?
I'm just laughing at the collection of practices that seem to exist.
It looks like it could be.
It's like a karuta.
It was like a karuta.
Sad background music
Hey, Ano...
What's up?
I have a question. Is this a good time?
Um... oh, my God.
No, no, no, now, now, okay? Um... oh, God.
No, not now.
What?
I can't join your circle of friends.
What do you want me to do?
Why are you saying that?
Because a circle of friends is just a circle.
It's a circle that can be broken.
It's easy to break a circle.
If you're alone...
It won't break. It can't be broken.
So you don't have to be in a circle.
Holding hands all the time.
It's too much work, isn't it?
So I don't think you have to try to get in the circle, but this is more important.
I understand. Thank you very much.
I'm standing up.
Business.
Business?
Yes, business.
Business means work, right?
Is this how you usually refer to business now, Kan-chan?
Well, I guess it's like representing something.
I think business is like this in my mind.
It's done! Done! What is business? I was told to take off my clothes by a big adult.
I'm doing business with my body.
That's my image.
Actually, I don't know.
So the girls get paid for taking their clothes off? I don't know...
So the girls get paid for sewing?
Yes.
From this person?
No, not from this person.
She's the one who makes the money.
Oh, that big guy.Oh, that great guy.
Yeah.
And the great man will take all the money.
This person makes money.
I have no intention of doing it myself.
That's business.
What's so blue about him?
His face is blue.
I can tell when I see them.
I can tell when I see him, like he's this kind of obnoxious adult. I can tell when I see him, like, "This person is such a nasty adult.
I can see all kinds of juices coming out of him. From his face, from his mouth.
He doesn't even realize it.
You mean he's a bad adult? Yes. That's why I don't think you should obey a powerful person.
You shouldn't follow them just because they're powerful.
People like this are never scary.
Be careful. Don't be misled. Ama-chan Channel, please subscribe to our channel!